Guide to the Anne Ramsay Somers Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, 1975-1981; Accession 1984-M-007; 5 linear feet (12 boxes)
  - South Carolina Hospital Association, 1981 January 22 (Box 10, Folder 160)
  - McAnley Health Center, 1981 January 30 (Box 11, Folder 161)
  - University of Michigan, 1981 January 31 (Box 11, Folder 162)
  - Promoting Health, 1981 January-February (Box 11, Folder 163)
  - OLVF Foundation, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 164)
  - American College of Hospital Administrators, 1981 February 18 (Box 11, Folder 165)
  - Princeton Hospital, 1981 March 6 (Box 11, Folder 166)
  - New England Hospital Assembly, 1981 March 31 (Box 11, Folder 167)
  - The Geriatric Imperative, book, 1981 April 1 (Box 11, Folder 168-169)
  - Health Care Commentary HIAA newsletter, 1981 April (Box 11, Folder 170)
  - National Council on Aging, 1981 April 1 (Box 11, Folder 171)
  - New Jersey Gerontological Society, 1981 April 3 (Box 11, Folder 172)
  - Loyola Medical Center, 1981 April 7 (Box 11, Folder 173)
  - Ohio State lecture, 1981 April 9 (Box 11, Folder 174)
  - Barrert Memorial Hospital, 1981 April 15 (Box 11, Folder 175)
  - NJHA meeting, 1981 April 29 (Box 12, Folder 176)
  - Central New Jersey Jewish Home for the Aged, 1981 May 6 (Box 12, Folder 177)
  - Southeastern Hospital Conference, 1981 May 12 (Box 12, Folder 178)
  - Patient Care article, 1981 May 15 (Box 12, Folder 179)
  - Jewish Institute for Geriatric Care, 1981 May 15 (Box 12, Folder 180)
  - Leavenworth Health Services, 1981 May 28 (Box 12, Folder 181)
  - New York Academy of Medicine, 1981 June 24 (Box 12, Folder 182)
  - NCOA Journal, 1981 July-August (Box 12, Folder 183)
  - Patient Care interview, 1981 August (Box 12, Folder 184)
  - Mobius article, 1981 August (Box 12, Folder 185)
  - Journal of Health Politics, Policy & Law article, 1981 September (Box 12, Folder 186)
  - Chief Executives Forum, 1981 September 22 (Box 12, Folder 187)
  - Ross Health Administration Forum, 1981 September 23 (Box 12, Folder 188-189)
  - Conference on Health Promotion and Physical Fitness in New Jersey, 1981 October 1 (Box 12, Folder 190)
  - Medical Society of New Jersey, 1981 October 5 (Box 12, Folder 191)
  - HRET retreat, 1981 October 10 (Box 12, Folder 192)
  - United Hospitals Medical Center Symposium, 1981 October 14 (Box 12, Folder 193)
  - Institute for Health Studies Conference - Iona College, 1981 October 22 (Box 12, Folder 194)
  - Georgetown University Conference on Gerontological Nursing, 1981 October 26 (Box 12, Folder 195)
  - Trustee article, 1981 November (Box 12, Folder 196)
  - Princeton University meeting, 1981 November 11 (Box 12, Folder 197)
- Additional Material, 1972-1989; Accession 1989-M-082; 6 linear feet (6 boxes)
  Addition inventory by Carol King 1989 July. Received from: Anne Ramsay Somers, 1989 May 8
  - Correspondence
    - A-Z, 1979-1989 (Box 1)
  - Writings and Project Files
    - Blue Shield: Denenberg Hearings, Pennsylvania, 1972 (Box 2)
    - Federal Health Education Policies: Health Insurance Benefits Advisory Council (HIBAC), 1973-1975 (Box 2)
    - TV violence and consumer health education: task force recommendations, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
    - Working papers of New England Journal of Medicine ( NEJM ) article, "Violence, Television and the Health of American Youth", 1975-1976 (Box 2)
    - TV violence: efforts to counteract it including media response to NEJM article, 1975-1977 (Box 2)
    - National Institute of Health: expert panel on consumer health education, 1975-1977 (Box 2)
    - Reviews and responses to task force publication, Prodist edition, of Health Promotion and Consumer Health Education, chaired by ARS, 1975-1978 (Box 2)
    - Requests for reprints of NEJM articles, 1976 (Box 2)
    - Public Law 94-317: Title I, Health Information and Health Promotion, 1976 (Box 2)
    - Reviews and responses to task force publication, Aspen edition, of Promotion Health: Consumer Education and National Policy, edited by ARS (Box 2)
    - Reader response: Letters to ARS and NEJM, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
    - Office of Health Information and Health Promotion (OHIHP), 1976-1977 (Box 2)
    - Duke University Medical Center: conferences on the private sector, 1976-1980 (Box 2)
    - Institute of Medicine (IOM): Board on Health Promotion and Disease Prevention, 1976-1982 (Box 2)
    - American College of Physicians (ACP), 1977-1980 (Box 2)
    - Excerpta Medica, publisher of Journal of Patient Counselling and Health Education, 1977-1982 (Box 2)
    - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1977-1982 (Box 2)
    - Family and Community Health, 1977-1982 (Box 2)
    - Johnson & Johnson, 1977-1983 (Box 2)
    - Diabetes Care, 1977-1984 (Box 2)
    - National Fund for Medical Education, 1977-1985 (Box 2)
    - Institute of Medicine: advisory committee on surgeon general's report, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
    - Irving Ladimer: project on the role and responsibility of the health consumer, 1978-1981 (Box 2)
    - Inquiry, 1978-1984 (Box 2)
    - Healthy America, the National Coalition for Health Promotion, 1979 (Box 3)
    - Harvard School of Public Health: sabbatical, 1979-1980 (Box 3)
    - Lewis E. Weeks' project, oral history of health care leaders, 1979-1981 (Box 3)
    - Industrywide Network for Social, Urban and Rural Efforts (INSURE), 1979-1983 (Box 3)
    - "Management Medicine" section of Patient Care, 1979-1984 (Box 3)
    - Retirement Research Foundation: grant proposal to develop a federal-state long-term care program for the elderly, 1980-1981 (Box 3)
    - Case Western Reserve University: Health Systems Management Center, 1980-1983 (Box 3)
    - Wayne State University School of Medicine, 1980-1983 (Box 3)
    - Wayne State paper, "What Price Prevention? Approaches to the Organization and Delivery of Preventive Services in Primary Care," by Anne Somers, 1981 January 5 (Box 3)
    - "Issues: Other Views," Promoting Health, summary of "Health Promotion: The Second Public Health Revolution", 1981 January-February (Box 3)
    - White House Conference on Aging, 1981 April (Box 3)
    - George Washington University: National Health Policy Forums, 1981-1982 (Box 3)
    - Foreward by ARS to Promoting Health Through Risk Reduction, 1981 July-1982 April (Box 3)
    - Catholic Health Association (CHA); "Pro-competition: Some Second Thoughts, Old Issues, New Directions," Hospital Progress, 1981 November-1982 January (Box 3)
    - Case Western Reserve University, 1981-1984 (Box 3)
    - Aspen Systems Corporation: general, 1981-1985 (Box 3)
    - Journal of the American Medical Association, 1982 (Box 3)
    - University of California, San Francisco, 1982 February 8 (Box 3)
    - Long Island University, 1982 March 2 (Box 3)
    - Aspen Institute, San Antonio "Incorporating Preventive Health Services into Primary Care: One Approach to Primary Health in the Elderly", 1982 March 8 (Box 3)
    - Monmouth College paper, "Taking Charge of your Own Health", 1982 March 25 (Box 3)
    - Mid Atlantic Health Congress paper, "The Geriatric Imperative: What Role for the Hospital?", 1982 May 18 (Box 3)
    - Easton Hospital, Pennsylvania, 1982 May 20 (Box 3)
    - University of Connecticut commencement address, "The Geriatric Imperative: A Major Challenge to the Health Professions", 1982 May 29 (Box 3)
    - Washington, D.C. Medicare Conference paper, "Rethinking Medicare to Meet Future Needs", 1982 June 17 (Box 3)
    - "Anne Ramsay Somers In First Person: An Oral History," edited by Lewis Weeks, 1982 July (Box 3)
    - Ontario Council of Health workshop, 1982 July 6 (Box 3)
    - NEJM, "Long-term Care for the Elderly: A New Health Priority", 1982 July 22 (Box 3)
    - Journal of Gerontological Nursing "Aging in Perspective: The Evolution of Medical and Social Policy", 1982 August (Box 3)
    - United States General Accounting Office, Washington, D.C., 1982 August-December (Box 3)
    - NATO Advance Research Institute Conference on Health Services Systems paper, "Health Services in the United States: Groping Toward A 'System'?", 1982 August-September (Box 3)
    - "Preventive Health Services for the Elderly: The Rutgers Medical School Project," by Anne Somers Leona Kleinman, and William Clark, Inquiry, 1982 Fall (Box 3)
    - Home Health Agency Conference paper, "Medicare and Long-Term Health Services", 1982 September 15 (Box 3)
    - "Moderating the Rise in Health Care Costs: A Different View," NEJM, 1982 October 7 (Box 3)
    - Caldwell B. Esselstyn Foundation, 1982 October 7-9 (Box 3)
    - Rutgers Conference on Policy Issues in Work and Retirement, 1982 October 14-15 (Box 3)
    - Institute of Medicine paper, "Medicare and Medicaid: Their Role in Preventive Health Services for the Elderly", 1982 October 21 (Box 3)
    - Case Western Reserve University paper, "The Growing Female Gerontocracy: Peril or Promise?", 1982 October 21-22 (Box 3)
    - Institute of Medicine of Chicago, 1982 October 23 (Box 3)
    - Montefiore Hospital and Medical Center, 1982 November 6 (Box 3)
    - Saskatchewan Health-Care Association Annual Convention, 1982 November 8 (Box 3)
    - American Public Health Association paper, "Are We Preventing Prevention For The Elderly?", 1982 November 17 (Box 3)
    - Health Matrix, 1982 Winter (Box 3)
    - Project Hope Conference paper, "Long-Term Care for the Elderly and Disabled: An Urgent Challenge to the 'New Federalism'", 1982 December 10 (Box 3)
    - Advisory Council on Social Security, 1982 December 12 (Box 4)
    - Dean's lunch: transparencies and outline of the "Rise in Health Care Costs", 1982 December 17 (Box 4)
    - European Health Policy Forum, 1982-1983 (Box 4)
    - Office of Technology Assessment, Washington, D.C., 1982-1984 (Box 4)
    - Möbius, 1983 January (Box 4)
    - UCLA Geriatric Seminar, 1983 January 20 (Box 4)
    - University of Southern California-California Hospital Association paper, "Competition And/Or Regulation in a New Environment", 1983 January 28 (Box 4)
    - Submission to Newsweek entitled "Wanted: A Viable LTC Policy!", 1983 February (Box 4)
    - New Jersey Health Sciences Group, 1983 February 8 (Box 4)
    - Veterans Administration Task Force on the Geriatric Plan, 1983 March 4 (Box 4)
    - Johns Hopkins University, School of Hygiene and Public Health (Karen Davis project between the United States and Japan on aging and health policy research), 1983 March 14 (Box 4)
    - National Council on the Aging, Inc., 33rd Annual Conference, 1983 March 16 (Box 4)
    - Kentucky Medical Association Conference, 1983 March 17 (Box 4)
    - House Select Committee on Aging, testimony of Anne Somers, 1983 March 28 (Box 4)
    - American Association for World Health, 1983 April 7 (Box 4)
    - Columbia University paper, "Liberty and Equity in Health Policy: A Consumer Perspective", 1983 April 15 (Box 4)
    - Western Gerontological Society paper, "The Challenge of Health Promotion for the Elderly," by Anne Somers and Victoria D. Weisfeld, 1983 April 18 (Box 4)
    - Mt. Sinai Medical Center paper, "Financing Long-Term Care: A Suggested Public Sector Approach", 1983 April 21 (Box 4)
    - New York Academy of Medicine paper, "Revising the Balance of Health Benefits and Fixed Physicians' Fees", 1983 April 29 (Box 4)
    - Hospitals, "The Geriatric Imperative", 1983 May 1 (Box 4)
    - Caldwell B. Esselstyn Foundation, 1983 May 5-7 (Box 4)
    - Beverly Hospital Spring Symposium paper, "The New Health Care Environment: Major Challenge to the Community Hospital", 1983 May 13-14 (Box 4)
    - Academy of Medicine of New Jersey Citizens Award, 1983 May 25 (Box 4)
    - Home Health Agency Assembly of New Jersey, Inc., 1983 May 26 (Box 4)
    - American Public Health Association, 1983 June 5-7 (Box 4)
    - New York Academy of Medicine, "Prevention, Geriatrics, and Medical Education", 1983 June 6-7 (Box 4)
    - Duke University Medical Center, "And Who Shall Be The Gatekeeper?", 1983 June 16 (Box 4)
    - St. Peter's Medical Center, 1983 August 12 (Box 4)
    - Prudential Insurance Company of America, 1983 September 14 (Box 4)
    - Squibb Institute for Medical Research paper, "The Geriatric Imperative: An Urgent Challenge to the Health Professions", 1983 September 27 (Box 4)
    - Snope Conference (Institute on Aging, Rutgers University), 1983 September 28 (Box 4)
    - Washington Business Group on Health, 1983 Fall (Box 4)
    - Long-term care, 1983 October (Box 4)
    - Medical Economics, "As Their Problems Spread, So Will Yours," by Charlotte L. Rosenberg, 1983 October 3 (Box 4)
    - Ross Health Administrative Forum, 1983 October 5-7 (Box 4)
    - Hahnemann University, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, National Health Constitutional Convention, 1983 October 24 (Box 4)
    - Michigan State University, Haak-Lilliefors Memorial Lectureship on Aging, 1983 October 27-28 (Box 4)
    - New York State Journal of Medicine, "Home Health Care: Home Birthing to Hospice Care," by Allen D. Spiegal, review by Anne Somers, 1983 October-November (Box 4)
    - Columbia University paper for the Mayoral Conference on Alzheimer's Disease and Related Orders, "Major Issues in Financing Long-Term Care With Special Reference to Alzheimer's Disease", 1983 November 3 (Box 4)
    - New Jersey Academy of Family Physicians paper, "Is Comprehensive Care for the Elderly Fiscally Viable?", 1983 November 9 (Box 4)
    - Philadelphia Yearly Meeting of the Religious Society of Friends paper, "The Elderly, Health Care, and Fiscal Viability", 1983 November 19 (Box 4)
    - Inquiry, "And Who Shall Be the Gatekeeper?", 1983 Winter (Box 4)
    - Senate Finance Subcommittee on Health Hearings on Long Term Care, 1983 November (Box 4)
    - Rutgers Medical School Conference on "Issues in Public Health: Toward the Twenty-First Century", 1983 December 10 (Box 4)
    - "Paying for Health Care: Major Trends and Issues," Environmental Medicine Course, 1983 December 20 (Box 4)
    - National Board of Medical Examiners, 1983-1986 (Box 5)
    - Office of Technology Assessment, Washington, D.C., 1984 January (Box 5)
    - Letter to the editor, The New York Times, 1984 February 6 (Box 5)
    - Brookdale Center on Aging at Hunter College, New York, "Some Thoughts on Medicare Reform", 1984 February 9 (Box 5)
    - Assistant Hospital Directors Association (AHDA) of New Jersey, 1984 February 21 (Box 5)
    - Senate Committee on Aging Hearings on Long-Term Care, Bill Bradley presiding, 1984 February 27 (Box 5)
    - National Institute on Aging and the Beverly Foundation paper, Washington, D.C., "Long-Term Care for the Elderly: Policy and Economic Issues", 1984 March 26 (Box 5)
    - Roger Williams General Hospital, A Geriatric Symposium, 1984 April 10 (Box 5)
    - University of Connecticut Health Center, Symposium on Geriatrics, 1984 April 11 (Box 5)
    - New Jersey Association of Non-Profit Homes for the Aging paper, "The Changing Environment, New Imperatives, and New Challenges to the Health Care Industry", 1984 May 1 (Box 5)
    - Home Health Care of St. Luke's Inc., Kansas City, Missouri, 1984 May 11 (Box 5)
    - Rutgers University Institute for Research on Women, 1984 May 22 (Box 5)
    - Goldwater Memorial Hospital, 1984 June 6 (Box 5)
    - Canadian College of Health Service Executives, National Conference, 1984 June 12 (Box 5)
    - Center for Health Facilities Research, Neil Weisfeld, director, 1984 June 19 (Box 5)
    - Rutgers Seminar entitled "The Graying of New Jersey: Covering Issues of Aging in the Mass Media," (Aumente Conference), 1984 June 21 (Box 5)
    - Health state, 1984 July (Box 5)
    - St. Vincent's Nursing Home paper, "Health Care for the Elderly: The Growing Dilemma and Some Suggested Adjustments", 1984 July 2 (Box 5)
    - Andrew Stein, President of the Borough of Manhattan, hearing on Home Care, 1984 July 10 (Box 5)
    - New England Journal of Medicine, "Why Not Try Preventing Illness As A Way of Controlling Medicare Costs?", 1984 September 27 (Box 5)
    - Institute of Medicine (IOM) paper, "The Increase in Demand for Health Services: A Historical Perspective and Some Thoughts For the Future", 1984 October 10 (Box 5)
    - Rutgers Medical School Symposium in honor of Professors Anne R. and Herman M. Somers, 1984 October 12 (Box 5)
    - Hahnemann University, Second Session of the National Health Constitutional Convention, 1984 October 15 (Box 5)
    - Council on New Jersey Affairs, 1984 October 25 (Box 5)
    - Princeton University graduate student workshop on Medicare Reform, 1984 Fall (Box 5)
    - Principles of Geriatric Medicine, 1984 Fall (Box 5)
    - National Research Council paper, "Keeping Our Health Care System Healthy", 1985 February (Box 5)
    - University of Texas Health Science Center, Houston, "Some Random Thoughts on Health Promotion and the Elderly Inspired by Frank Williams' Paper", 1985 April 17-18 (Box 5)
    - Catholic Health Association of the United States, 1985 May (Box 5)
    - The Teaching Nursing Home, chapter 5 "Long-Term Care for the Elderly" by ARS, 1985 May (Box 5)
    - Health Education Center, Pittsburgh, Pennslyvania, 1985 May 23 (Box 5)
    - Medford Leas Board of Trustees, N.J., "Medicare 1985: Some Long-Term Problems and Issues", 1985 June 26 (Box 5)
    - International Association of Gerontology, XIII Congress, 1985 July 13 (Box 5)
    - James J. Florio Symposium, 1985 July 29 (Box 5)
    - The New York Times, "Dr. Reagan Can Use President Reagan's Help", 1985 August 2 (Box 5)
    - New Jersey conference on aging veterans, 1985 September 11 (Box 5)
    - Graduate Program in Public Health, Rutgers, 1985 Fall (Box 5)
    - Journal of the Medical Society of New Jersey, "Can the Elderly Afford to be Sick?", 1985 October (Box 5)
    - The New York Times, "Let Us Wage War on Preventable Disease", 1985 October 3 (Box 5)
    - University of Medicine and Dentistry of New Jersey (UMDNJ), Grand Rounds, 1985 October 8 (Box 5)
    - Florida International University paper, "Rethinking Medicare to Meet Future Needs", 1985 October 10-11 (Box 5)
    - Friends Meeting, 1985 October 12 (Box 5)
    - New Jersey Public Health Association, 1985 October 16 (Box 5)
    - Oregon Health Decisions, Inc., conference on biomedical ethics, 1985 October 22 (Box 5)
    - Ohio Department of Aging, 1985 October 23 (Box 5)
    - NEJM, "Antitrust Law Versus Peer Review," by Leigh Dolin, 1985 October 31 (Box 5)
    - Institute of Medicine, Washington, D.C., 1985 November (Box 5)
    - American Academy of Medical Directors, 1985 November (Box 5)
    - UMDNJ Conference Flexner: 75 Years Later, A Current Commentary on Medical Education, 1985 November 11 (Box 5)
    - Business and Health, "Health Promotion for the Elderly: 1985 Update," by Anne R. Somers and Victoria D. Weisfeld, 1985 December (Box 5)
    - Maxcy-Rosenau Public Health and Preventive Medicine, chapter 25, "Individual Behavior and Health," by ARS and Victoria Weisfeld, 1985 December (Box 5)
    - UMDNJ- Rutgers Medical School Lecture Series, 1985 December 3, 11 (Box 5)
    - Home Health Agency Assembly of New Jersey, Inc., conference program on long-term care, 1986 March 7 (Box 5)
    - New Jersey Hospital Association, conference on health care and the elderly, 1986 March 14 (Box 5)
    - American Medical Colleges, Northeast Group on Student Affairs, Philadelphia, "Four 'Orphan' Areas in Current Medical Education: What Hope for Adoption?", 1986 April 3 (Box 6)
    - UMDNJ Death and Dying Program, 1986 April 8-9 (Box 6)
    - University of Rochester Medical Center health-care symposium, 1986 April 11 (Box 6)
    - UMDNJ Fellowship Seminar Series on the Socio-Economic Aspects of Geriatrics, 1986 April 25 (Box 6)
    - University of California, Academic Geriatric Resource Program, 1986 May 16 (Box 6)
    - East Orange General Hospital, "The Geriatric Imperative: the Challenge to New Jersey Hospitals", 1986 May 22 (Box 6)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS), "Preventive Health Services for the Elderly", 1986 May 27 (Box 6)
    - Center for Corporate Public Involvement, Washington, D.C., "Health + Fifty: A New Concept for the Health Insurance Industry", 1986 June 26 (Box 6)
    - Colby Family Practice Continuing Education Conference, Waterville, Maine, 1986 July 18 (Box 6)
    - American Society of Internal Medicine, "Long Term Care: Hungry Stepchild of the U.S. Health Care System," The Internist, 1986 September (Box 6)
    - University of Tennessee, Memphis, "Four 'Orphan' Areas in Current Medical Education: What Hope for Adoption?", 1986 September 6-9 (Box 6)
    - Health Care organization and Administration (HCOA), Graduate Program in Public Health, UMDNJ, 1986 Fall (Box 6)
    - University of Pennsylvania, conference on Medicare, 1986 October 8-10 (Box 6)
    - Pennsylvania Public Health Association, "Preventive Gerontology: Contradiction in Terms or Key to Future Health Care?", 1986 October 9-10 (Box 6)
    - Hospitals, "NJ hospitals react to the 'geriatric imperative'", 1986 October 20 (Box 6)
    - Inquiry "The Changing Demand for Health Services: A Historical Perspective and Some Thoughts for the Future", 1986 Winter (Box 6)
    - National Council On The Aging, Inc., Perspective on Aging, 1986 Nov/December (Box 6)
    - The Times, two-part article on clinical aspects of geriatrics, 1986 December 22-23 (Box 6)
    - 55 Plus, 1987 January 22 (Box 6)
    - Business and Health, "Personal perspective: Is prevention better than cure? You had better believe it", 1987 March (Box 6)
    - Comprehensive Services on Aging (COPSA), conference on Alzheimer's Disease, 1987 March 13 (Box 6)
    - University of California, Los Angeles, public lecture series on aging, "Tackling the Long-Term Care Crisis: an Individual Action Program for Older Americans", 1987 March 17 (Box 6)
    - American Association of Retired Persons (AARP), Long-Term Care Advisory Committee, 1987 March 30 (Box 6)
    - Hastings Center Report, letter to the editor, 1987 April (Box 6)
    - "U.S. Long-Term Health Care Policy: Goals, Programs, Financing, and Guiding Principles", 1987 April (Box 6)
    - Princeton University, Leadership in the Modern Presidency, 1987 April 3-4 (Box 6)
    - University of Colorado Health Sciences Center, "Financing Long-Term Health Care", 1987 April 9 (Box 6)
    - GPPH Seminar on Long-Term Care, 1987 April 21 (Box 6)
    - Robert Wood Johnson Medical School, Geriatric Seminar, 1987 April 24 (Box 6)
    - Delaware Valley Hospital Council, Inc., "The Geriatric Imperative: The Challenge to U.S. Hospitals", 1987 May 6 (Box 6)
    - Senior Citizens Council of Union County, N.J., Inc., "Tackling the Long-Term Care Crisis: an Individual Action Program for Older Americans", 1987 May 7 (Box 6)
    - Advisory Council on Education for Health, subcommittee on preventive gerontology and long-term care, 1987 May 21 (Box 6)
    - Monmouth Medical Center, Alzheimer's Disease Update Conference, 1987 May 28 (Box 6)
    - Area Health Education Center (AHEC), Charlotte, North Carolina, statewide conference on the evolution in health care, 1987 May 28-30 (Box 6)
    - Greater Southeast Management Center, 1987 June 24 (Box 6)
    - NEJM, "Insurance for Long-Term Care: Some Definitions, Problems, and Guidelines for Action", 1987 July 2 (Box 6)
    - AHEC's program on solutions to financial dilemmas of Alzheimers, 1987 July 7 (Box 6)
    - Health Affairs, letter to the editor, 1987 Summer (Box 6)
    - National Center for Health Statistics, Public Health Conference on Records and Statistics, "Aging in the 21st Century: Projections, Personal Preferences, Public Policies: A Consumer View", 1987 July 12-15 (Box 6)
    - Medford Leas, New Jersey, 1987 October 3 (Box 6)
    - The World View of Paul Cézanne: A Psychic Interpretation, introduction by Seth, 1987 October 4-7 (Box 6)
    - Blue Cross, Blue Shield of Pennsylvania, Eleventh Annual Pocono Conference on Health Care, 1987 October 16 (Box 6)